Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 49, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Collective agreements on working conditions and employee benefits in the Ontario Public Service, 1978; Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Labour and politics, 1971; Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Author: David B. Archer
  - Item 9: Labour and politics, 1971; Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Stewards' handbook: labour legislation in Ontario, 1969; Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Labour. Research Dept.
  - Item 11: Stewards' handbook: labour legislation in Ontario, 1969; Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Union Officers' handbook, Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Union Officers' handbook, Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Collective agreement for CAAT Support Staff 1977-1978, Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Collective agreement for CAAT Support Staff 1977-1978, Publication (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Box: 49, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: OFL Summary of the Federal White Paper "Unemployment Insurance in the 70's", 1970; Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: O F L facts and figures, 1971; Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: O F L facts and figures, 1971; Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: O F L facts and figures, 1974; Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: O F L facts and figures, 1974; Publication (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Box: 49, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Immigrant women: their untold history, 1988; Publication (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Author: Joyce Scane
- Box: 49, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Women speak, 1988; Publication (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Author: Marjatta Holt
- Box: 49, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Brant Principals & Vice-Principals, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Author: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Atikokan Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Borden CFB Principals & Vice-Principals, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Bruce Principals & Vice-Principals, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Carlton Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Central Algoma Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Chapleau Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Cochrane-I.F. Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Dryden Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Dufferin Principals & Vice-Principals, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Durham Principals & Vice-Principals, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Crleton Principals & Vice-Principals, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Atikokan Principals & Vice-Principals, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Ontario Secondary School Teachers - Pay scales /Atikokan Principals & Vice-Principals, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Written collective agreement for the period 1 January 1976 to 31 August 1977 inclusive between the Board of Education for the City of London and the Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federtion (District 4), 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Box: 49, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Espanola, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Espanola, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Espanola, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Hearst, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Hearst, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Essex, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Notes:
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Etobicoke, 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Etobicoke, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Elgin, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Espanola, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Fort Frances - Rainy River, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Essex, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Frontenac, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Geraldton, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Grey, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Haldimand, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Halburton, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Halton, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Hastings, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Hornepayne, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Huron, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Box: 49, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kent, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kent, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board James Bay Lowlands, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kapuskasing, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kenora, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kent, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Kirkland Lake, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Lake Superior, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Lakehead, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Lambton, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Lanark, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Leeds-Grenville, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Notes: Jan. 76-Aug. 77
  - Item 13: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Lennox-Addington, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Box: 49, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Oxford, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Manitoulin, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Middlesex, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Muskoka, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Nipigon-Red Rock, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Nipissing, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Norfolk, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board North Shore, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board North Shore, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Northumberland-New Castle, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Ottawa, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Ottawa, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Oxford, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Norfolk, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Box: 49, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Peel, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Peel, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Perth, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Petawawa CFB, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Peterborough, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Prescott-Russell, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Prince Edward, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Red Lake, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Renfrew, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Red Lake, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Box: 49, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Sault Ste. Marie, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Simcoe, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Stormont-Dundas-Glengarry, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Stormont-Dundas-Glengarry, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Sudbury, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Timiskaming, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Timmins, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Victoria, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Wellington, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Waterloo, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board West Parry Sound, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Simcoe, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board Simcoe, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement -- Board West Parry Sound, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Box: 50, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Handbook, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Handbook, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Box: 50, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Handbook, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Handbook, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Box: 50, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Handbook, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Handbook, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Box: 50, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: At what cost?: Issues in Secondary Education: an introduction to the Study of the Role of the Secondary School in Ontario, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation. Provincial Research Committee
- Box: 50, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective agreement between Ontario Hydro and Canadian Union of Public Employees - C.L.C., Ontario Hydro Employees' Union, Local 1000: April 1, 1980 - March 31, 1982, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Box: 50, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Convention collective de travail entre la communaute urbaine de Montreal, 1980; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Author: Communaute Urbaine de Montreal
  - Item 2: Convention collective de travail entre le conseil de securite de la C.U.M., 1974; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Convention collective de travail entre le conseil de securite de la C.U.M., 1974; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Collective agreement between the M.U.C. Security Council (hereinafter called "the Employer") and the Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc. (hereinafter called "the Brotherhood") for the period 1st January 1974 to 31st December 1974, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Author: Communaute urbaine de Montreal (Quebec)
  - Item 5: Collective agreement between the M.U.C. Security Council (hereinafter called "the Employer") and the Montreal Urban Community Policemen's Brotherhood Inc. (hereinafter called "the Brotherhood") for the period 1st January 1974 to 31st December 1974, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Collective agreement: 1st January 1972 to 31st December 1973, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Author: Fraternite des policiers de Montreal
  - Item 7: Modifications a la convention collective des policiers de la communaute urbaine de Montreal, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Box: 50, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Convention collective de travail entre la Communaute Urbaine de Montreal, 1983; Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Erreurs et oublis releves a la convention collective, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Box: 50, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report submitted to the Commission of inquiry into labor relations between the City of Montreal and the Montreal Policemen's Brotherhood, 1970; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Box: 50, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board of Canada and the Canadian Postmasters and Assistants Associaiton: Group: Revenue Postal Operations (All Employees), Code: 610/81, Expirty Date: 31 December 1981 = Convention entre le conseil du tresor du Canada et, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Author: Canada. Treasury Board, Canadian Postmasters and Assistants Association
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board the Professional Associaiton of Foreign Service Officers: Group: Foreign Service (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Association professionnelle des Agents du Service exterieur: Groupe: Ser, 1975; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Author: Canada. Treasury Board, Professional Association of Foreign Service Officers
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board the Professional Associaiton of Foreign Service Officers: Foreign Affairs Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Association professionnelle du Service exterieur: Groupe: Exterieures (, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Box: 50, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Sciences biologiques (tous les e, 1975; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Canada. Treasury Board, Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Veterinary Science (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Me, 1975; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Scientific Regulation (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe:, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Mathematics (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Mathemati, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Forestry Group (all employees) = Conventions entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Sciences Fore, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Psychology Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Psychologie, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Pharmacy Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Pharmacie (tou, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Box: 50, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Economics, Sociology and Statistics (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Can, 1976; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Physical Sciences Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Scien, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Social Work Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Service Soc, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Chemistry Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Chimie (tous, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Computer Systems Administration (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Group, 1976; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Engineering and Land Survey (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Gro, 1976; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Aircraft Operations Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Nav, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Architecture & Town Planning Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Gr, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Box: 50, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Dentistry (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Art Dentaire, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Agriculture Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Agriculture, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Commerce (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Commerce (tou, 1975; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Home Economics Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Sciences, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Library Science Group (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Bibliot, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Professional Institute of the Public Service of Canada: Group: Translation (all employees) = Convention entre le Conseil du Tresor et l'Institut Professionnel du Service Public du Canada: Groupe: Traduction, 1975; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)